https://www.cisco-eagle.com/catalog/topic/privacy

Login
View Cart (0)
View Quote (0)
Checkout
Quote Builder
Call Today!
Inquire: Privacy Concerns
We respect and protect your privacy This is the privacy policy for Cisco-Eagle, Inc. Our homepage on the Web is located at http://www.cisco-eagle.com. We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy. You may contact us by mail, phone, or e-mail as shown below:
Cisco-Eagle, Inc.
2120 Valley View Lane
Dallas, Texas 75234
E-mail: 24hours@cisco-eagle.com
Phone: 1-888-877-3861
Data Collection
For each visitor to our Web page, our server automatically recognizes the consumer's domain name where possible. Customers who have asked us for assistance through various channels may be identified to help serve those needs.
We collect aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit through web server logs. This process is to help us analyze our site. Our web server logs do not identify who a visitor is, collect email addresses, or other personal information.
The information we collect is used for internal review. It is used to improve the content of our Web page, or to customize the content and/or layout of our site for each individual visitor.
Cookies are small data files which record information, and are stored on your hard drive while you are browsing our site. We only use cookies to record session information, such as keeping track of items that are added to the shopping cart in our online catalog.
Information You Provide Us
Some information volunteered by our visitors is collected and kept. This includes survey information and/or site registrations, product specification inquiry forms, and the e-mail addresses of those who purchase products through our online catalog.
We do not sell or share any of your information with a third party, and we do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. We never provide the e-mail addresses of our visitors to anyone else.
The only exception being when an order is placed using our online catalog. Then we will share sufficient information with the freight company to facilitate shipment of the product ordered. If a product needs to be shipped from one of our suppliers, we will provide them only the shipping and product information needed to have the products you have ordered shipped to your address.
Secure Transactions
We employ the services of Norton Secured powered by Verisign to handle secure online payments, using state of the art encryption.
Customer Contact Data
Postal addresses
If you supply us with your postal address you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events.
If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling,
e-mailing, or writing to us using the contact information shown at the top of
this page.
Telephone numbers
If you supply us with a telephone number, we will only contact you by telephone as required to take care of a request you made for more information, or to facilitate an order you placed with us in our online catalog.
E-mail Addresses
If you supply us with an e-mail address, we will use it to take care of a request you made for more information or to facilitate an order you placed with us in our online catalog. We may also e-mail you from time to time within the strict limits of Federal Can-Spam law.
You have the option of being notified of changes or updates to our website by filling out the form at http://www.cisco-eagle.com/Register/Index.htm
Future Use
If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site; on this page, to notify you and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.
If there should be an issue or concern about this security policy, please notify us using the contact information at the top of the page, and we will work with you to resolve any issues.
CCPA Compliance
We comply with all applicable privacy laws. You can make a personal information request twice in a
12-month period. We must collect specific information from you to verify your identify when this request occurs.
We will respond to your request within 45 days of receipt.
Under CCPA, California citizens have these rights:
The right to request disclosure of any data we collect about you, including the categories of personal information we collect, its method of collection,
our use of that information, any sell or disclosure (and the categories of that information) disclosed or sold to any third parties. Upon request, we will disclose
the information we collect, how, and the categories thereof.
You have the right to view any personal information we collect.
Upon request, we will provide a copy any specific information collected about you during the 12 preceding months
through a personal information request.
You have the right to have your personal information deleted. Upon request, we will delete your personal information from our database(s), except for any exceptions as prescribed by CCPA.
You have the right to deny any selling of your personal data. (Cisco-Eagle does not sell personal information to third parties).
You have the right not to be discriminated against because you exercised any of the previous rights.
Personal information collection
In compliance with CCPA, these are the categories of personal information we have collected the past twelve months. Many records to not include all of the items below.
Names
Email addresses
Telephone numbers
Physical or mailing addresses, including nation, state, city and postal codes
Product interests
Collection methods: Website users who complete web inquiry forms, chats, online quoting or ecommerce purchases provide all or part of the information listed above.
Interactions with Cisco-Eagle (in person or by phone) or at trade shows may also be a source of the information. Third parties, such as vendors with whom we work, may sometimes provide
us with personal information from customers who have requested assistance.
Personal information usage: This information is used in the following ways:
To fulfill requests for assistance, information or quotation.
To fulfill orders, ship products or comply with other customer needs and other business purposes.
To assist with any billing or remittance efforts.
To enhance sales and marketing efforts.
To respond to requests for disclosure of personal information.
Personal information sales the last 12 months: Personal information is not sold by Cisco-Eagle.
Disclosures the past 12 months: We sometimes disclose customer information to third parties to execute business, as noted below:
Performance of required financial audits.
Performing services on behalf of customers, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing
customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, installing equipment, verifying customer information,
shipping equipment, or other business processes. Parties that may receive this information include installation companies, shipping companies,
equipment manufacturers, or other parties who assist in project implementation.
We do not retain credit card records. However, that information is passed to a secure gateway provider.
Some data is integrated between Cisco-Eagle and marketing services providers.
To respond to requests for disclosure of personal information.
How to submit a personal information request
By phone: call 888-877-3861 toll-free.
By website request: Email 24hours@cisco-eagle.com
To comply with your request, we may ask for specific information that allows us to identify you in our databases.
Shopping Cart:
0
Items
Your shopping cart is currently empty.
Checkout
Discounts:
Total:
View cart
Your Quote:
0
Items
Your wish list is currently empty.
Build Your Quote
Add to Cart
Total:
Loading...
